<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on misuohho&#39;Blog</title>
        <link>https://misuohho.github.io/en/post/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on misuohho&#39;Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Misuohho_blog</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 12:39:16 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://misuohho.github.io/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>All Black Myth Wukong Voice Actors &amp; Cast List</title>
        <link>https://misuohho.github.io/en/p/all-black-myth-wukong-voice-actors-cast-list/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 12:39:16 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://misuohho.github.io/en/p/all-black-myth-wukong-voice-actors-cast-list/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://misuohho.github.io/wk.jpg" alt="Featured image of post All Black Myth Wukong Voice Actors &amp; Cast List" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;【Black Myth: Wukong】is an action RPG developed by Game Science, and it’s based on the Chinese mythological figure Sun Wukong, otherwise known as the Monkey King himself. It can be a rather talkative game too, so here’s a rundown of the voice actors and cast list of Black Myth: Wukong.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;table-of-contents&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Table of contents&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;[TOC]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;all-voice-actors-in-black-myth-wukong&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All Voice Actors in Black Myth: Wukong&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There actually isn’t a lot of information publicly available about the voice cast of &lt;em&gt;Black Myth: Wukong&lt;/em&gt; at the time of writing, so we’ll update this section as more info comes our way. However, a handful of the major characters from the game have been named, as listed below:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mark-ota-as-sun-wukong&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mark Ota as Sun Wukong&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mark Ota takes on the lead role of &lt;em&gt;Black Myth: Wukong&lt;/em&gt;, as the titular Monkey King, Sun Wukong. Mark Takeshi Ota is no stranger to the video game world, as he’s voiced Hachiro from &lt;em&gt;Rise of the Ronin&lt;/em&gt;, Edmundis Magarus in &lt;em&gt;Baldur’s Gate 3&lt;/em&gt;, and has also done additional voices for games like &lt;em&gt;Dead Island 2&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Company of Heroes 3&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;jack-ayres-as-zhu-bajie&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jack Ayres as Zhu Bajie&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jack Ayres plays Zhu Bajie, who typically looks like an adorable human-sized pig man in the Chinese mythology stories, but has taken on a vastly different appearance in &lt;em&gt;Black Myth: Wukong&lt;/em&gt;. Ayres broke into the video game industry a few years ago, and has been in games like &lt;em&gt;Warhammer 40K: Rogue Trader&lt;/em&gt; and Banishers: &lt;em&gt;Ghosts of New Eden&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;leader-looi-as-pingping&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leader Looi as Pingping&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our last known voice actor for &lt;em&gt;Black Myth: Wukong&lt;/em&gt; is Leader Looi, who voices Pingping. Most notably, she voices Gigina, Yume, and Hakugin in &lt;em&gt;Eiyuden Chronicle: Hundred Heroes&lt;/em&gt;. She’s also done voice work for &lt;em&gt;Fortias Saga&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Tales of Grimm&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And those are all of the known voice actors for &lt;em&gt;Black Myth: Wukong&lt;/em&gt; for now. There are plenty of other credits to get through, including the ones for some &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.escapistmagazine.com/all-black-myth-wukong-bosses-listed/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;major boss fights&lt;/a&gt;, and we’ll update this article as more info comes out.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
